Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics Graduate School of Nutrition student records, 1940-1974.
New York State College of Home Economics Graduate School of Nutrition student records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Home Economics Graduate School of Nutrition student records, 1940-1974.
23-11-2780
New York State College of Home Economics. Graduate School of Nutrition.
5 cubic ft.
Printed Materials
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Applications, grades, credits transferred, and letters of recommendation.
ORGANIZATIONAL HISTORY
On March 14, 1974 the Board of Trustees voted to abolish the Graduate School of Nutrition and the Department of Human Nutrition and Food in the College of Human Ecology and to establish the Division of Nutritional Sciences, an intercollege unit within the Colleges of Agriculture and Life Sciences and Human Ecology.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Applications, grades, credits transferred, and letters of recommendation.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Home Economics.; Cornell University--Students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
During student's lifetime individual student records restricted to permission of student and office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Ackerman, Bernard, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
- Addy, Nicole Andree, 1968-1970 (Box 1)
- Adjarian Marinozi, Rose Louise, 1953-1955 (Box 1)
- Ahmed, Myrna Mintz, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Aines, Philip Deane Jr., 1949-1951 (Box 1)
- Albert, Jeanette, 1948-1950 (Box 1)
- Alcazar, Beatriz Sara, 1961-1963 (Box 1)
- Almroth, Eva Stina, 1973-1976 (Box 1)
- Along, Carmel, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
- Anderson, John Burdette, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
- Andrew, Elizabeth Marie, 1974-1977 (Box 1)
- Ankrah, Clara Inkumsah, 1962-1963 (Box 1)
- Armstrong, Carolyn Marie, 1958 (Box 1)
- Arzaga, Velona L., 1950-1952 (Box 1)
- Atinmo, Taiwo Jokotola, 1971-1973 (Box 1)
- Badger, Jane Anne, 1960-1962 (Box 1)
- Balmer, Joanne P., 1971-1973 (Box 1)
- Barnwell, John L., 1951-1953 (Box 1)
- Barua, Javier Castaneda, 1954-1956 (Box 1)
- Bates, Margaret Westbrook, 1948-1950 (Box 1)
- Bauer, Adelia, 1946-1948 (Box 1)
- Beaudry, Micheline Marie Nicole, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
- Becker, Norwin Howard, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
- Bedrosian, Karakian, 1954-1956 (Box 1)
- Benda, Stepan, 1953 (Box 1)
- Bernard, Rudy Andrew, 1958-1960 (Box 1)
- Bhamarapravati, Anotai, 1954-1956 (Box 1)
- Bistany, Roland, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
- Black, Robert Seymour, 1954 (Box 1)
- Blair, Dorothy Ann, 1972-1975 (Box 1)
- Bliss, Cheryl Roberta, 1972-1974 (Box 1)
- Blondin, Joan, 1959-1961 (Box 1)
- Blumenthal, Ralph, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
- Bocobo, Dulce Laurel, 1948-1952 (Box 1)
- Bogan, Alison Davidson, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Boggs, Dallas Ervin, 1954-1955 (Box 1)
- Blonde, Jean Anne Thomas, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
- Boss, June, 1953-1955 (Box 1)
- Bourdeau, Constance Ernestine, 1958-1960 (Box 1)
- Bowering, Jean Lucy, 1962-1964 (Box 1)
- Bowman, Ronald Nelson, 1958-1960 (Box 1)
- Boyar, Andrea Phyllis, 1972-1975 (Box 1)
- Brachfeld, Bernard A., 1949-1951 (Box 1)
- Bradfield, Robert, 1951-1952 (Box 1)
- Brambila, Sergio, 1958-1960 (Box 1)
- Brand, Kathleen (Hilfinger), 1947-1949 (Box 1)
- Brin, Myron, 1946-1948 (Box 1)
- Brown, Ann Margaret, 1955-1957 (Box 1)
- Brunell, Harvey J., 1946 (Box 1)
- Bubeck, Margaret, 1949-1951 (Box 1)
- Bunton, Mildred Settle, 1949-1953 (Box 1)
- Burgess, William H., 1949-1950 (Box 1)
- Bush, Harold LaVern, 1950-1952 (Box 1)
- Butow, Ronald A., 1958-1960 (Box 1)
- Callmer, Eva Helena, 1971-1974 (Box 1)
- Campbell, George Latimer Jr., 1950-1951 (Box 1)
- Campbell, Mary Barkley, 1953-1955 (Box 1)
- Caplan, Evelyn Ann, 1957-1960 (Box 1)
- Causey, Kathryn, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
- Celozzi, Evemarie, 1952-1954 (Box 1)
- Chang, Edith Yu-Hsia, 1966-1968 (Box 1)
- Chassy, Judith M. Price, 1963-1965 (Box 1)
- Chen, Belle Pei-li, 1953-1955 (Box 1)
- Chen, Ruth Chih-Ann, 1965-1967 (Box 1)
- Chiang, Michael, 1952-1954 (Box 1)
- Chu, Irene Yen-Ping, 1959-1961 (Box 1)
- Ciaccio, Edward, 1953-1955 (Box 1)
- Clary, John J., 1959-1961 (Box 1)
- Cohen, Arnold D., 1949-1951 (Box 1)
- Cohen, Isadore, 1947-1949 (Box 1)
- Coombs, John Bennett, 1967-1972 (Box 1)
- Coulston, Sister Ann, 1969-1972 (Box 1)
- Crandall, Joyce J., 1949-1952 (Box 1)
- Dalme, Claire, 1947-1949 (Box 2)
- Daries, Marianne Ruth Moore, 1949-1950 (Box 2)
- Darragh, Richard, 1953-1955 (Box 2)
- Desai, Kalpakam Shankar, 1961-1964 (Box 2)
- Di Giacomo, Maria Michele, 1916-1963 (Box 2)
- Doane, Brenda Darrah, 1970-1972 (Box 2)
- Donnelly, Elizabeth Ann, 1947-1949 (Box 2)
- Drummond, M. Therese, 1973-1975 (Box 2)
- Drury, Elizabeth Anne, 1956-1957 (Box 2)
- Einset, Eystein, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
- Elford, Roberta Maurer, 1961-1963 (Box 2)
- Ellison, Joan M., 1948-1950 (Box 2)
- Empey, Elizabeth Louise, 1954-1956 (Box 2)
- Englberger, Lois Noellsch, 1971-1974 (Box 2)
- Estevez, Silvia Elena, 1960-1963 (Box 2)
- Evans, Margaret Angela, 1970-1974 (Box 2)
- Feher, Joseph John, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
- Ferrari, Richard Alan, 1953-1955 (Box 2)
- Finkin, Ruth Mrs Thomas, 1947-1949 (Box 2)
- Flores, Marina, 1952-1953 (Box 2)
- Fogg, Verne Allen Jr., 1951-1952 (Box 2)
- Fonrose, Harold A., 1952-1954 (Box 2)
- Formica, Santo Domonick, 1947-1948 (Box 2)
- Frane, John A., 1950-1952 (Box 2)
- Frank, Stefan Sebastian, 1953-1955 (Box 2)
- Frankel, Donna Lucas, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
- Franklin, Ruth Elizabeth, 1948-1950 (Box 2)
- Fridriksdottir, Sigrun Kristin, 1952-1953 (Box 2)
- Fullmer, Curtis Sheridan, 1969-1972 (Box 2)
- Furr 2nd, Harold Clark, 1972-1975 (Box 2)
- Gardner, Bernard Jay, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
- Garrett, Roger Landis, 1958-1961 (Box 2)
- Ghering, Barbara Anne, 1956-1958 (Box 2)
- Gibbons, June Annette, 1974-1977 (Box 2)
- Gibbs 3rd, Thomas Maxwell, 1971-1974 (Box 2)
- Gillette Barbara Ann, 1952-1954 (Box 2)
- Goldstein, Jack, 1955-1957 (Box 2)
- Green, Armin J., 1962-1964 (Box 2)
- Greer, Betty Jean (Waldner), 1951-1953 (Box 2)
- Griffis, William R., 1949-1951 (Box 2)
- Grippin, Clifford Howe Jr., 1950-1952 (Box 2)
- Grossbeck, Helen M., 1962-1964 (Box 2)
- Grigsby, Harrison Gail, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
- Hale, Alice Ann, 1974-1977 (Box 2)
- Halstead, Peggy Kwan, 1973-1976 (Box 2)
- Harper, Robert B., 1968 (Box 2)
- Harrison, Earl Howard, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
- Hartdegen, Susan, 1957-1958 (Box 2)
- Hayden, Mavis Maud, 1961-1963 (Box 2)
- Hayes, Lesly Cecelia, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
- Heimberg, Murray, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
- Hepburn, Frank, 1946-1948 (Box 2)
- Heytler, Peter George, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
- Heywood, Peter Frank, 1969-1972 (Box 2)
- Hilary, Carol Ann, 1958-1960 (Box 2)
- Hill, Charles Horace, 1948-1949 (Box 2)
- Hoffman, Sigmund, 1947-1948 (Box 2)
- Hogan, Susan Miller, 1966 (Box 2)
- Hollis, Karlyn Joan, 1950-1951 (Box 2)
- Holmes, Susan Verity (Parkinson), 1948-1950 (Box 2)
- Hong, Leon, 1953-1957 (Box 2)
- Hopkins, Daniel T., 1958-1963 (Box 2)
- Hsu, Jean Shu-Tsu, 1968-1971 (Box 2)
- Huey, Janice Marie, 1952-1954 (Box 2)
- Huffman, Marcia Russel, 1960-1962 (Box 2)
- Hutter, Louise Frances, 1969-1972 (Box 2)
- Im, Haesook Kim, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
- Im, Wha Bin, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
- Ingram, Robert Hollister, 1946-1948 (Box 2)
- Jakobovits, Carol Callier, 1972-1975 (Box 2)
- Johnson, Allan Alexander, 1972-1974 (Box 2)
- Johnson, Sharon Louise, 1970-1973 (Box 2)
- Joiner, Marian Grace, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
- Kalaw, Josie Mayo, 1975 (Box 3)
- Kao, Wen Hui (Mrs Tsien), 1948-1950 (Box 3)
- Kase, Lawrence Emanuel, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
- Kaye, Alvin, 1948-1949 (Box 3)
- Kelley, Linda Lou, 1973-1977 (Box 3)
- Kerr, Marion Elizabeth, 1957 (Box 3)
- Kilbourne, Sylvia, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
- Kim, Ho Jik, 1948-1950 (Box 3)
- King, Frederick Jessop, 1950-1952 (Box 3)
- Kinney, Harrison B., 1948-1949 (Box 3)
- Kosinski, John Albert Jr., 1948-1950 (Box 3)
- Kostuk, Catherine Marion, 1957-1962 (Box 3)
- Kraft, Allen Abraham, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
- Krome, Alan, 1959-1961 (Box 3)
- Lafortune, Therese, 1954-1955 (Box 3)
- Lane, Irwin W., 1946-1948 (Box 3)
- Lee, Han-min, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
- Lee, Tee-Ping, 1964-1966 (Box 3)
- Lee, Yi-chuen (Loretta), 1968-1970 (Box 3)
- Lee, Young Chang, 1963-1965 (Box 3)
- Lengemann, Frederick William, 1949-1951 (Box 3)
- Levine, Charles Joseph, 1949 (Box 3)
- Lin, Ren-Tsong Lin, 1969-1971 (Box 3)
- Lipke, Herbert, 1947-1948 (Box 3)
- Liu, Chin Hsu, 1949 (Box 3)
- Litsche, Mildred Elizabeth, 1969-1972 (Box 3)
- Liu, Tung, 1972-1975 (Box 3)
- Lockwood, Richard Marvin, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
- MacDonough, Linda Ann, 1974 (Box 3)
- MacKenzie, Robert Earl, 1963-1965 (Box 3)
- MacPherson, Ann Elizabeth, 1964 (Box 3)
- MacQuarrie, Marnie Elaine, 1969-1971 (Box 3)
- Machlin, Lawrence, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
- Manniello, Maria Jane, 1958-1961 (Box 3)
- Martin, Thurman O'Neal, 1960 (Box 3)
- Martin, Arlene Patricia, 1950-1952 (Box 3)
- Martinez, Olga Beatriz, 1969-1971 (Box 3)
- Massaro, Ellen Rand, 1973-1975 (Box 3)
- Massaro, Thomas F., 1971-1973 (Box 3)
- Masse-Grenier, Priscille, 1971-1974 (Box 3)
- Mayo, Raquel Diasanta, 1964 (Box 3)
- McGarry, Patricia Mary, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
- McGowan, Joan Austin, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
- McKee, Betty Ann, 1952-1954 (Box 3)
- Mendelsohn, Dorothy Helen, 1954-1955 (Box 3)
- Mendiola, Leticia Ramos, 1953-1955 (Box 3)
- Menges, Jane Evelyn, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
- Meyers, Bernard, 1951-1953 (Box 3)
- Michel, Frank, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
- Miller, Robert, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
- Miller, William Laubach, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
- Molleson, Ann, 1949-1952 (Box 3)
- Monder, Carl, 1950-1952 (Box 3)
- Moodie, Celia Jean, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
- Morris, Edward, 1946-1948 (Box 3)
- Morrisey, Sister Leona, 1966-1969 (Box 3)
- Morrow, Sarah Linda MacDonough, 1966 (Box 3)
- Mukhopadhyay, Sunit Kumar, 1963-1965 (Box 3)
- Munford, Robert, 1952-1954 (Box 3)
- Nakamura, Karen Kay, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
- Nettleton, Joyce Adele, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
- Neely, Carol Sue, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
- Noble, Edwin Lee, 1955-1957 (Box 3)
- Norton, Jane Sinden, 1957-1959 (Box 3)
- Nott, Constance Veronica, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
- Odell, Sandra Jean, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
- Ogunmodede, Bankole Kayode, 1965-1966 (Box 3)
- Oh, Se Kyung, 1966-1968 (Box 3)
- Ottey, Leo J., 1950-1952 (Box 3)
- Overly, Darlene Joan, 1955-1957 (Box 3)
- Palasiri, Ubolsri, 1953-1955 (Box 3)
- Pilcher, Helen Leona, 1947-1949 (Box 3)
- Pitz, Edward W., 1946-1947 (Box 3)
- Pillet, Bernard Daniel, 1965-1967 (Box 3)
- Prevost, Elizabeth Allen, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
- Pritchard, Alan Bryan, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
- Pompey, Josephine, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
- Pyrek, Janine Dolores, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
- Rand, Catherine Evelyn, 1969-1971 (Box 4)
- Ravenscroft, Catherine, 1964-1966 (Box 4)
- Reber, Elwood, 1947-1948 (Box 4)
- Rechcigl, Miloslav, 1954-1955 (Box 4)
- Redder, Anna May, 1946-1948 (Box 4)
- Reed, Dwight Earl, 1948-1951 (Box 4)
- Reid, Ian Maitland, 1963-1965 (Box 4)
- Reingold, George, 1948-1949 (Box 4)
- Remington, Mary Margaret, 1970-1974 (Box 4)
- Resnick, Nancy, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
- Rice, Andrew Cyrus, 1949 (Box 4)
- Rieley, Penelope Byrne, 1960-1962 (Box 4)
- Ringler, Ira, 1951-1953 (Box 4)
- Robertson, Marion Susan, 1963-1965 (Box 4)
- Robinson, Robert James, 1947 (Box 4)
- Ross, Alta Catharine, 1970-1972 (Box 4)
- Roth, Jerome Allan, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
- Rothman, Deborah, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
- Rovics, Jack Joseph, 1950-1952 (Box 4)
- Roza, Martha Lucia, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
- Rush, Karl Cook, 1961 (Box 4)
- Ryan, Thomas J., 1953 (Box 4)
- Sachs, Barbara Charlotte D'Asaro, 1951-1953 (Box 4)
- Sambhavaphol, Poonsakdi, 1954-1955 (Box 4)
- Santavicca, Edward A., 1973 (Box 4)
- Santos, Erlinda L., 1960 (Box 4)
- Sanz, Bernabe Perez, 1958 (Box 4)
- Sault, Frances Marguerite, 1960-1962 (Box 4)
- Sauer, Frederick, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
- Schaffel, Lawrence, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
- Scheier, Genevieve Estella, 1949-1951 (Box 4)
- Schneider, Donald M., 1953-1954 (Box 4)
- Schlosser, Robert A., 1963-1966 (Box 4)
- Schnake, Mary Lisbeth, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
- Schotland, Ronald Seth, 1955 (Box 4)
- Schwieger, Marjorie Louise (Mrs Jack E. Ross), 1960-1962 (Box 4)
- Seelbach, Charles William, 1948 (Box 4)
- Serraon, Virginia Ulanday (Mrs Jose P. Claudio), 1954-1956 (Box 4)
- Sheppard, Herbert, 1947-1949 (Box 4)
- Shapiro, Ralph, 1956-1957 (Box 4)
- Silver, Alan Herbert, 1954-1956 (Box 4)
- Sipin, Sonia Sison, 1965-1967 (Box 4)
- Skellenger, Marie L., 1950-1952 (Box 4)
- Skipwith, Hope Ely, 1961 (Box 4)
- Smitasiri, Tin Nee, 1956-1958 (Box 4)
- Smith, George C., 1955-1957 (Box 4)
- Smulson, Mark Elliot, 1959-1962 (Box 4)
- Snider, Alisan, 1966-1969 (Box 4)
- Spaid, John Ferdinand, 1957-1960 (Box 4)
- Spence, Joseph Thomas, 1973-1975 (Box 4)
- Stephenson, Lani Sue, 1971-1973 (Box 4)
- Stetekluh, Robert Edward, 1956-1958 (Box 4)
- Stewart, Delores Ellen, 1972-1975 (Box 4)
- Swindell, Archie C., 1962-1964 (Box 4)
- Swisher, Charles Allen, 1947-1949 (Box 4)
- Tadayyon, Bahram, 1966 (Box 5)
- Tadayyon, Ency Whitehill, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
- Tallman, Donald Frederick, 1956-1958 (Box 5)
- Tan, Tiong-Hoey, 1964-1966 (Box 5)
- Tensuan, Rosalinda Salcedo, 1960-1961 (Box 5)
- Thim, Eleanore Elizabeth, 1951-1953 (Box 5)
- Thomas, Oswald Augustus, 1959-1961 (Box 5)
- Tonseth, Ernst Ivar, 1952-1956 (Box 5)
- Torres, Wanda Iris, 1964 (Box 5)
- Trupin, Joel S., 1954-1956 (Box 5)
- Tsuji, Ichiro, 1946-1948 (Box 5)
- Tu, Shiao-chun, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
- Tung, Yvonne Roh-ran, 1950-1952 (Box 5)
- Tunison, John R., 1050-1952 (Box 5)
- Turk, Donald Earle, 1955-1957 (Box 5)
- Tuthill, Sally Anne, 1957-1958 (Box 5)
- Valle-Riestra, Jose Victor Ricardo, 1963-1965 (Box 5)
- Van Buren, Jerome P., 1059-1951 (Box 5)
- Wang, Shu-Heh, 1965-1967 (Box 5)
- Watson, Katherine E. L., 1970-1973 (Box 5)
- Wei, I-Ying (Mrs Samuel Lee), 1962 (Box 5)
- Weiss, Steven R., 1949-1950 (Box 5)
- White, Evelyn Offei, 1971-1973 (Box 5)
- White, Venesa Joy, 1969-1971 (Box 5)
- Wilkins, Charles N. Jr., 1950-1952 (Box 5)
- Wilson, Barbara Prescott, 1966-1968 (Box 5)
- Wishnetsky, Theodore, 1948-1950 (Box 5)
- Witheiler, Alan P., 1963-1966 (Box 5)
- Wolfson, Edward Albert, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
- Wolgemuth, June Carol, 1970-1973 (Box 5)
- Wood, Ansel Scott, 1951-1953 (Box 5)
- Wood, Betty Ellen (Mrs Alvin W. Ries), 1949-1950 (Box 5)
- Wood, Norris Philip, 1949-1951 (Box 5)
- Woods, Margo Nicki (Mrs Margo Schuster), 1962-1964 (Box 5)
- Yacowitz, Harold, 1946-1948 (Box 5)
- Yang, Chung Shu, 1963-1965 (Box 5)
- Yang, Ming-Whui Wang (Shirley), 1971-1973 (Box 5)
- Yang, Hui Lan (Mrs David H. Cheng), 1949-1950 (Box 5)
- Yanni, Jane Brinkley, 1967-1971 (Box 5)
- Yap, Bwee Hwa, 1957-1960 (Box 5)
- Ying, Beatrice P., 1961-1963 (Box 5)
- Young, Doris Louise, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
- Yu, Josephine Tsung-tsung, 1965-1967 (Box 5)
- Zablan, Thelma Aguilar, 1959-1961 (Box 5)
- Zampelas, Demetrios, 1953-1955 (Box 5)
- Zelleznick, Barbara Ann, 1971-1975 (Box 5)
- Zweerink, Hendrik Jan, 1965 (Box 5)
- Minutes of the Meetings of the Faculty of the School of Nutrition, 1943-1959 (Box 6)
- Committee on Policies, 1949-1965 (Box 6)
- Graduates, School of Nutrition, 1947-1965 (Box 6)
- Graduate School Candidates, 1950-1960's (Box 6)
- Graduate School of Nutrition, Registrar's Office - Course Offerings (Box 6)
- Graduate School of Nutrition, Registrar's Office (Admissions to School) (Box 6)
- Graduate School of Nutrition, Room Use Survey (Box 6)
- School Registration by Term, 1953 (Box 6)
- Student Records - Policy (Box 6)
- Treasurer's Office - List of Assistantships (Box 6)
- Graduate Proposals (Box 6)
- Graduate School of Nutrition - List of Applicants for the Master's Program, 1960-1970's (Box 6)